<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FootBall Club</string>

    <!--array for FootBall Club name-->
    <string-array name="club_name">
        <item>Barcelona FC</item>
        <item>Real Madrid FC</item>
        <item>Bayern Munchen FC</item>
        <item>Manchester City FC</item>
        <item>Manchester United FC</item>
        <item>Chealse FC</item>
        <item>AC Milan FC</item>
        <item>Arsenal FC</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--array resource FootBall club-->
    <array name="club_image">
        <item>@drawable/barcelona</item>
        <item>@drawable/realmadrid</item>
        <item>@drawable/bayer</item>
        <item>@drawable/manchestercity</item>
        <item>@drawable/manchesterunited</item>
        <item>@drawable/chealse</item>
        <item>@drawable/acmilan</item>
        <item>@drawable/arsenal</item>
    </array>

    <!--array description for FootBall club-->
    <string-array name="club_description">
        <item>Futbol Club Barcelona, known simply as Barcelona and colloquially as Barça, is a professional football
            club based in Barcelona, Catalonia, Spain
        </item>
        <item>Real Madrid Club de Fútbol, commonly known as Real Madrid, is a professional football club based in
            Madrid, Spain
        </item>
        <item>Fußball-Club Bayern München e.V., commonly known as FC Bayern München, FCB, Bayern Munich, or FC Bayern,
            is a German sports club based in Munich, Bavaria (Bayern)
        </item>
        <item>Manchester City Football Club, commonly known as City, is a football club in Manchester, England. Founded
            in 1880 as St. Marks (West Gorton)
        </item>
        <item>Manchester United Football Club, commonly known as Man. United or simply United, is a professional
            football club based in Old Trafford, Greater Manchester, England, that competes in the Premier League
        </item>
        <item>Chelsea Football Club is a professional football club in London, England, that competes in the Premier
            League. Founded in 1905, the clubs home ground since then has been Stamford Bridge
        </item>
        <item>Associazione Calcio Milan, commonly referred to as A.C. Milan or simply Milan, is a professional football
            club in Milan, Italy, founded in 1899.
        </item>
        <item>Arsenal Football Club is a professional football club based in Islington, London, England, that plays in
            the Premier League, the top flight of English football
        </item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
